theamm.org 2016-10-27

# AMM Privacy Policy

#### Effective: January 19, 2011

This Privacy Policy describes American Marriage Ministries’s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. American Marriage Ministries receives your information through our website _www.theamm.org_. For example, you submit personal information when you become an ordained minister through the American Marriage Ministries web site. 

When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by American Marriage Ministries in the United States or any other country where American Marriage Ministries operates. 

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:info@theamm.org "Contact American Marriage Ministries"). 

* * *

## Information Collection and Use

We collect and use your information to provide accountability for our ordination records. 

Information Collected Upon Registration: When you create or reconfigure an American Marriage Ministries account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, password, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name, is listed publicly on our web site, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, public user profiles and viewing lists, do not require registration. 

Additional Information: You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography, or a picture. We may use your contact information to send you information regarding inquiries about solemnizing marriage or other minister church functions. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional. 

Other Public Information: Our Services are primarily designed to help you perform marriage for friends and family members. 

Log Data: Our servers automatically record information (“Log Data”) created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, and the referring domain. Other actions, such as interactions with our website, applications and advertisements, may also be included in Log Data. 

Cookies: Like many websites, we use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our web site such as searching and looking at public user profiles. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk. American Marriage Ministries may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our web site, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

Third Party Services: American Marriage Ministries uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our web site and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request. 

* * *

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not disclose your private information except in the limited circumstances described here. 

Your Consent: We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client or application to access your American Marriage Ministries account. 

Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy. 

Law and Harm: We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect American Marriage Ministries’s rights or property. 

Non-Private or Non-Personal Information: We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did). 

* * *

## Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are ordained through American Marriage Ministries, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account. 

You can also permanently delete your American Marriage Ministries account. If you follow the instructions contact us at info@theamm.org and request that your ordination be revoked and your account canceled, your account will be deactivated and then deleted. When your account is deactivated, it is not viewable on the American Marriage Ministries web site. 

* * *

## Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at info@theamm.org. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account. 

* * *

## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at **http://www.theamm.org/privacy-policy**. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the web site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? Please [contact us](mailto:info@theamm.org "Contact American Marriage Ministries").
